

# **OLAKUNLE IBRAHIM**

## • DETAILS •

Sweden 0736565835 klexy2402@gmail.com

> Driving license B

> > LINKS

WEB-Portfolio

o SKILLS o

Communication Skills

Good team player

Flexibility and Adaptability

Data Engineering (BigQuery, Tensorflow)

Data Analysis (Power BI, Qlik, Excel))

Machine Learning (Data Modelling and Training - KNIME)

Programming Language (Java, C#, JavaScript, Python)

Development Framework (React.js, Vue.js, Node.js, Spring Boot & JPA, Selenium, Jenkins, TeamCity, Ghostlab, Android Studio)

Database (MySQL, NoSQL, MongoDB)

Cloud Computing (Google Cloud, MS Azure, AWS)

UI/UX

**Digital Marketing** 

HOBBIES

Travelling, Football, Chess game, Gym

#### PROFILE

Experienced in design, building, Implementation, testing, integration, delivery, and maintenance of software systems. Proficient in different development platforms, programming languages, data engineering and analytic, machine learning, artificial and business intelligence, and information system management. Experienced with the latest development tools, technologies, and procedures. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Software / Data Specialist (Freelancer) at TISV Digital, Atlanta, Georgia. & Lagos, Nigeria
December 2018 — Present

- Developing and architecture training on software systems, systems test to identify failure points and ensure quality software for release to production.
- Performing continuous integration and delivery of product quality.
- Retrieving and integrating data between several databases.
- Working with data quantitative and qualitative analysis.
- · Working with clients to gather requirements. Agile methodology

#### Cashier/ Assistant/ IT Support at Hubertus Restaurant, Stockholm

August 2015 — December 2016

- Worked productively with Restaurant Team to provide better customer service experience and ensure customer satisfaction at all time.
- Booking and mailing correspondences.

#### Local Assistant at EFMAB, Stockholm

January 2015 — July 2015

• Cleaning and hall management

# Computer Specialist at Softline Communication Company, Ado Odo

June 2006 — June 2012

- Worked on data input, data management, and electronic data transfer.
- Bulk messaging and emailing.
- Ensuring database security and integrity.
- Develop IT equipment, process related documents and system applications

# Production Manager at Narconon Nigeria (NGO), Lagos

June 2007 — May 2012

- Worked to ensure plans execution and successful.
- Developed strategies for events and productivity and project lead.
- Coordinate partnership and corroborate UNODC concepts.

#### Special Assistant, Legislative Arm at House of Representative, Lagos/Abuja

June 2009 — May 2012

- · Coordinate youth empowerment and development programs.
- Special duties and social engagement.

# • LANGUAGES •

English

Swedish

#### System Administrator at Expert Services, Lagos

June 2004 — June 2006

- Install, upgrade and monitor software, hardware and networks.
- Monitoring system performance and troubleshooting issues.

# Hardware Software Technician at YNS Technology, Lagos

June 2003 — June 2004

- Support and maintain in-house technology equipment and IT systems.
- Configuring and repairing hardware and software application for optimal performance.

## EDUCATION

Master of Science in Information System, Lund University, Lund

August 2020 — June 2021

Bachelor of Science in Software Development, Kristianstad University, Kristianstad

August 2017 — June 2020

Diploma in Computer Science, Kwara State Polytechnic, Ilorin

September 2001 — December 2003

## CERTIFICATION

Salesforce Certified Platform Developer 1 - Training

December 2021

**AWS Certified Solution Architect - Training** 

November 2021

Data Engineering with Google Cloud

October 2021

Digital Marketing Certificate, Google Fundamental Digital Marketing

April 2019

# Y EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Courses Project at Kristianstad University, Lund University.

2017 - 2021

Application development, BI application, Data analysis, Data modeling, and Research Study.

Assistant Field Communicator/ Reporter at BBC, Lagos

2009 - 2010

Radio 5 Lagos.

**Documentary about Nigeria Cultures and Traditions** 

Lead Field Communicator at UK DragonFly TV, Lagos

2010 - 2010

**Project: Lagos Documentary** 

#### ■ REFERENCES

• References available upon request